# JAN CROSS-ZAMIRSKI

jc856@cam.ac.uk \https://crosszamirski.github.io/

### **SUMMARY**

I am PhD student under the supervision of Professor Carola-Bibiane Schönlieb in the Cambridge Image Analysis group at DAMTP, University of Cambridge. We collaborate with Dr Yinhai Wang and the Quantitative Biology group at AstraZeneca.

### **EDUCATION**

Cambridge Image Analysis Group, DAMTP, University of Cambridge

2018 - 2022

Ph.D. Candiate

Supervisors: Professor Carola-Bibiane Schönlieb, Dr. Yinhai Wang

Natural Sciences - Physics, University of Cambridge

2017 - 2018

Master of Science (MSci), Part III

Research Project: Machine Learning Tools for Predicting Cognitive Health with Professor Zoe Kourtzi

Director of Studies: Professor Pietro Cicuta

Natural Sciences - Physics, University of Cambridge

2014 - 2017

Bachelor of Arts (BA), Part II

Projects: Computational, Experimental
Director of Studies: Professor Mark Warner

### **EXPERIENCE**

AstraZeneca January 2019 -

Quantitative Biology research group

Bank of America Merrill Lynch

June 2017 - August 2017

Summer Analyst. Equities electronic trading, portfolio and ETF trading

BNP Paribas June 2016 - September 2016

Summer Analyst. Automated market making, fixed income flow trading

Isaac Physics August 2013 - September 2014

Content creator at https://isaacphysics.org/

### PUBLICATIONS AND PREPRINTS

Self-Supervised Learning of Phenotypic Representations with Weak Labels

Preprint (2022).

**Jan Cross-Zamirski**, Elizabeth Mouchet, Guy Williams, Carola-Bibiane Schönlieb, Riku Turkki & Yinhai Wang

https://github.com/crosszamirski/WS-DINO

Label-Free Prediction of Cell Painting from Brightfield Images

Sci Rep 12, 10001 (2022).

**Jan Cross-Zamirski**, Elizabeth Mouchet, Guy Williams, Carola-Bibiane Schönlieb, Riku Turkki & Yinhai Wang

https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-022-12914-x

### SELECTED AWARDS

## UKRI-BBSRC DTP Studentship Award

2018 - 2022

Fully Funded Ph.D. studentship from the BBSRC, supported by AstraZeneca.

Total award value: £100,000

# Hawks Charitable Trust Recipient

2019 - 2022

Awarded anually for academic and sporting excellence while competing for CUCC and CUAC.

Total award value: £1000

# Corpus Project Prize for Natural Sciences (Physics)

2018

For those in their final year who achieved first-class marks for a dissertation or project

Full Blue 2018 - 2021

Cambridge University Cricket Club (CUCC).

Full Blue and First Class debut

Academic Scholar 2006 - 2013

Academic Scholar at the Perse School

### TALKS AND CONFERENCES

# AstraZeneca PhD Student Symposium

April 2021

Presented Poster

CytoData2020 October 2020

Attendee

MICCAI 2020 October 2020

Attendee

# MedTech Boost - Cambridge MemTech

September 2019

Awarded prize for the best impact on healthy ageing with innovative solutions for early detection of dementia.

### **TEACHING**

### **Undergraduate Supervisor**

2019 - 2020

Natural Sciences Tripos, University of Cambridge.

Supervised the Mathematical Biology course at Jesus College and St. Catharine's College.

Freelance Tutor 2014 -

A-Level Mathematics and Physics, university admissions tutoring,

English as a Foreign Language (TEFL).

### EXTRA INFORMATION

**Languages** Python, Matlab, R.

Packages PyTorch, Keras, Pandas, SciPy, NumPy

Software CellProfiler, ImageJ, MRIcron